{
	"data": [
		{
			"question": "When would you typically need to reassign leads from one user to another?",
			"answers": ["When a user departs from the sub-account"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "To bring in human touch points when necessary",
			"answers": [
				"To bring in human touch points when necessary",
				"Time-sensitive tasks",
				"Approval processes"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of setting up triggers for different calendar types?",
			"answers": [
				"To automate messaging and appointment-related actions, by ensuring that the trigger only fires when it should."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the significance of specifying 'recurring event type' as a trigger filter within a workflow?",
			"answers": [
				"It ensures the trigger is fired only for recurring appointments"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the essential requirement for the 'confirmed' appointment status trigger?",
			"answers": [
				"It ensures the system looks for a specific 'status' in the appointment trigger"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can 'non-confirmed' appointments statuses trigger/fire a workflow?",
			"answers": [
				"By using the 'new' status filter for the 'appointment status trigger.'"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'Calendars and Appointments' tab?",
			"answers": [
				"To provide a way to see each users calenders and appointments",
				"To show a daily, weekly or monthly overview of appointments and calendars",
				"To display daily appointments only",
				"To highlight past appointments"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you integrate your calendar into the system?",
			"answers": ["By connecting your Google and or Outlook calendar"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does an appointment marked as 'unconfirmed' mean?",
			"answers": ["It requires manual confirmation by the user"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is one of the prerequisites mentioned for using appointment booking features?",
			"answers": ["Creating a calendar widget and workflows for reminders"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users book an appointment on behalf of a contact from within a conversation?",
			"answers": [
				"By clicking the 'Book Appointment' button in the conversation preview or within the appointment tab"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can appointment status triggers be utilized in automation workflows?",
			"answers": [
				"To initiate follow-up actions based on appointment status changes"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you change the starting day of the week on your calendar?",
			"answers": ["Through account calendar preferences"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which meeting link option may not show up if it hasn't been integrated with the user's profile?",
			"answers": ["Zoom & Google Meet"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What's the difference between calendar availability and user availability?",
			"answers": [
				"Calendar availability reflects the business's start time and day of the week, while user availability specifies the user's working hours."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How does user availability impact appointment bookings?",
			"answers": [
				"It influences which team member's availability is considered when a lead books."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is the first row of a CSV file important?",
			"answers": ["It must not be blank"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the contact requirements need for the system to link data back to the contact?",
			"answers": ["An email or phone number"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which field type has case-sensitive and spelling-sensitive requirements?",
			"answers": ["Radio button"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is cleaning a CSV file important before uploading?",
			"answers": [
				"To prevent sending duplicate SMS",
				"To avoid duplicate messaging",
				"To improve contact organization"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the suggested approach to identifying duplicate values?",
			"answers": ["Highlight columns with conditional formatting"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "If not corrected, how are duplicate records typically handled when uploading the file?",
			"answers": ["The first duplicate is kept"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is the 'Remove Duplicates' function in Excel not recommended?",
			"answers": ["It removes entire contact records"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Who can access the 'Import Contacts' feature?",
			"answers": ["Location admin"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of using the 'None' option for unique identifiers?",
			"answers": ["To generate unique contact IDs for each row"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In the mapping view (before importing list), how are unmatched fields handled?",
			"answers": ["They can be manually mapped (custom fields) or skipped"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "When might you enable the 'Allow Duplicate Contacts' setting?",
			"answers": ["When importing contacts with shared email/phone numbers"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the benefit of using contact IDs as identifiers during import?",
			"answers": [
				"It helps create records for contacts using the contact ID instead of relying solely on email and phone numbers as the unique identifiers."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is one reason for exporting contacts and custom fields?",
			"answers": ["To perform data analysis in Excel"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following fields are included in the default export?",
			"answers": ["Name, email, phone B", "Create date, last activity", "Tags"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can additional custom fields be included in an export?",
			"answers": ["By selecting them in the 'columns' menu"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you choose specific contacts for export?",
			"answers": [
				"By selecting based on parameters set in your smartlist or manually checking the box next to the contacts name"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of smart lists?",
			"answers": ["To segment leads/contacts based on specific criteria."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In filtering, what is the function of 'and' conditions?",
			"answers": [
				"To combine multiple filters and find leads that meet all conditions."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'is not' filter option?",
			"answers": ["To exclude leads that meet a specific condition."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can smart lists be shared with other users?",
			"answers": [
				"By granting access to users within the 'Manage smart list' area."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of the Company Object feature in the CRM?",
			"answers": ["To facilitate communication within organizations"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the significance of the 'Company Object' feature when dealing with ",
			"answers": ["It centralizes all contacts into a single company entity."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of creating custom fields in the CRM?",
			"answers": ["To store specific information about contacts"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of creating and managing tasks within the system?",
			"answers": ["To remind individuals to complete specific actions."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following statements about task assignment is correct?",
			"answers": [
				"Tasks can be assigned to users, regardless of their connection to contacts."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of using internal notifications for task reminders?",
			"answers": ["To remind users about upcoming tasks."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the restore option in the contacts?",
			"answers": ["To recover accidentally deleted contacts in bulk"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is restored when you perform a bulk restore of contacts?",
			"answers": [
				"Conversation, Notes, Opportunities, Tasks, Appointments, Manual Actions."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you initiate the restoration of contacts individually from the 'Audit Logs'?",
			"answers": [
				"By selecting the 'Force Restore' option for the contact in the 'Audit Logs'"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of custom fields in contact records?",
			"answers": ["To create unique questions and data fields per contact"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can custom fields be organized for easier access?",
			"answers": ["By utilizing custom folders to group related fields."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What advantage does organizing custom fields into folders offer?",
			"answers": ["Better categorization and prioritization of information"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are bulk actions used for within the platform's contact tab?",
			"answers": ["Handling operations on a larger scale"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What types of bulk actions can be performed in the CRM?",
			"answers": ["Adding tags", "Sending emails", "Importing contacts"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In the context of bulk email campaigns, which factors can affect the data being returned to the CRM from bulk action(s)?",
			"answers": ["The SMTP provider used for sending emails"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users hide specific pipeline stages from the dashboard view?",
			"answers": [
				"By toggling the visibility settings located within the pipeline builder"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does marking an opportunity as 'Won' typically indicate?",
			"answers": [
				"The opportunity has been successfully 'Won' and moved out of the open stage."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the benefit of attributing a lead's value within the pipeline?",
			"answers": [
				"It visibly displays the dollar denomination of the lead for the opportunity."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of automating opportunities within pipelines?",
			"answers": ["To streamline and standardize opportunity management"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which automation trigger is suitable for moving contacts between stages?",
			"answers": ["Pipeline stage changed"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the 'Opportunity Status' action allow users to do?",
			"answers": ["Update the status of an opportunity"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of creating invoices in the system?",
			"answers": ["To keep track of expenses and get paid for services"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which section of the system should you navigate to in order to create invoices?",
			"answers": ["Payments"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you apply a discount to an invoice?",
			"answers": ["Manually add it after adding a product to the invoice"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which statement accurately describes the current capability of adding taxes?",
			"answers": [
				"Taxes must be manually added to invoices as they are not currently supported on checkout forms."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In the system, how are taxes associated with specific clients or business locations?",
			"answers": [
				"Taxes must be manually pre-built and linked to corresponding clients."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can taxes be integrated with SaaS payment links in the system?",
			"answers": [
				"Taxes are set up using the SaaS configurator for Stripe checkout."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which payment gateways can be integrated to enable the creation of invoices?",
			"answers": ["Both PayPal and Stripe"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of enabling auto-payment for recurring invoices?",
			"answers": [
				"To automatically charge the same card used for the first payment"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following statements are true about recurring invoices?",
			"answers": [
				"Recurring invoices can be created for subscription-based products.",
				"Discounts can be applied to items in recurring invoices.",
				"Recurring invoices can be scheduled to be sent monthly, weekly, or yearly."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following details are listed for each subscription?",
			"answers": ["Status of the subscription"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Who can access the Subscription page?",
			"answers": ["Users on any plan"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What filters are available on the Subscription page? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Subscription status"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What information is displayed on the Orders page?",
			"answers": ["Customer names, source of order, and order status"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Is the Orders page available for all pricing plans?",
			"answers": ["Yes"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What information about the ordered items can users find on the Orders page?",
			"answers": ["Item names and the quantity ordered"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the transactions page?",
			"answers": ["To track customer payments"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What information is displayed for each transaction on the transactions page?",
			"answers": ["Transaction date", "Payment source"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you filter transactions on the transactions page? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["By payment mode"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which section under the account or location should you navigate to in order to find products?",
			"answers": ["Payments"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which payment option listed below does NOT support products? (The user would need to manually input the monetary value)",
			"answers": ["Text to pay"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What Payment integrations are offered in the system? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Stripe", "Authorize.net", "Paypal", "NMI"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which type of products can be added to an order form?",
			"answers": ["Products that have been previously created/ imported"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What determines whether a product is a main product or a bump product?",
			"answers": [
				"A specific option is selected when adding the product to the page where it will be sold"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users verify the products added to the order form?",
			"answers": ["By previewing the page with the order form"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the text-to-pay links feature allow users to do?",
			"answers": ["Request manual payments through the Conversations tab"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What payment processor is needed to utlize the 'text-to-pay' links feature?",
			"answers": ["Stripe"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What can users customize when creating text-to-pay a payment request?",
			"answers": ["Product name, price, due date, and additional options"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the two main types of coupons mentioned in the video? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Fixed coupons", "Percentage coupons"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What can you restrict when creating a coupon? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Number of redemptions", "Specific products"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What information is needed to enable automatic sales receipts? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": [
				"Title",
				"Receipt prefix",
				"Receipt start number",
				"Email template"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which functionality is not available in payment settings?",
			"answers": ["Customizing payment links"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of adding tax information in payment settings?",
			"answers": ["To specify the tax rate and details for invoices"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of A/B split testing in email campaigns?",
			"answers": [
				"To analyze the success of subject lines and content variations"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the minimum number of contacts required for a split test with six variations?",
			"answers": ["60 contacts"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the 'version history' feature allow users to do?",
			"answers": ["Restore previous template versions"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is using email providers like Mailgun or LC email recommended?",
			"answers": ["They have direct API integration for better data tracking."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does RSS scheduling allow you to do?",
			"answers": ["Send emails in response to RSS feed updates."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In the context of email campaigns, what does the 'unique open rate' represent?",
			"answers": [
				"The percentage of contacts who opened the email at least once."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of a trigger link?",
			"answers": ["To attribute clicks and trigger actions in workflows."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which type of communication channels can trigger links be used in?",
			"answers": ["SMS and email"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can a trigger link be used to initiate a workflow?",
			"answers": [
				"By selecting the trigger link 'Trigger' in the workflow settings."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where can you find workflows within the system?",
			"answers": ["Automation tab of the sub account or location"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are workflow triggers?",
			"answers": ["Actions that initiate specific sequence of events"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the 'allow reentry' setting in workflows do when enabled?",
			"answers": ["Allows contacts to re-enter an active workflow"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following actions can be performed within workflows? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": [
				"Sending automated emails or SMS",
				"Assigning tasks to users"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the 'marked as read' setting in communication settings do?",
			"answers": [
				"Marks all outgoing automated messages as read in the conversation tab"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why would someone choose to build a workflow instead of using the default auto-missed call text-back feature in sub-accounts? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Throttle options"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the auto-missed call text back feature?",
			"answers": [
				"To prevent missed opportunities",
				"Quicker response to missed calls.",
				"Capture the leads interest before they move onto the next business"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where would a user disable the default auto-missed call text back feature for newly generated sub-accounts?",
			"answers": [
				"Within the business profile settings located in the sub-account settings"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'No Show Nurture' recipe?",
			"answers": ["To promote rescheduling after no-shows"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What trigger would be required for a No-Show workflow to fire/execute when the appointment status is set to 'No Show'?",
			"answers": [
				"'Appointment Status' triggers with an appointment status filter set to 'No-show'."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is it important to remove leads from the 'No Show Nurture' after booking?",
			"answers": [
				"To avoid overwhelming users with unintentional messages urging them to book, etc."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you grant a user access to a specific feature if they can't see it?",
			"answers": [
				"Adjust the user's permissions and ensure that the sub-account has the specific feature enabled within the agency view."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "On which subscription plan is the split-testing feature available in the Funnel Builder?",
			"answers": ["All subscription plans"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the process to add a product to a page in the Funnel Builder?",
			"answers": ["Create the product under payments, then add it to the page"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which option is NOT available under the settings section of the Funnel Builder?",
			"answers": ["adding a domains DNS records"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why can't a single domain be used for both hosting a website and sending emails?",
			"answers": [
				"Each domain must have a dedicated purpose to avoid conflicts"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does DNS propagation refer to?",
			"answers": ["The time it takes for DNS records to be added and mapped"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of a 'custom 404 page'?",
			"answers": ["To handle broken links and user input errors in URLs."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'layers' feature within the page builder?",
			"answers": [
				"To highlight specific sections and navigate within containers."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which elements can you add to your page to display videos?",
			"answers": ["Hosted videos, HTML5 videos, YouTube videos, and more."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'two-step order form' element?",
			"answers": [
				"It requires users to enter their contact details before proceeding to payment."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you customize the appearance of navigation menus in the page builder?",
			"answers": ["By adjusting spacing, colors, typography, and more."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What can you achieve by using the SEO metadata settings?",
			"answers": ["Optimize the page's appearance on search engine results."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is one of the main use cases of forms mentioned in the video?",
			"answers": ["Collecting data from users/leads"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'Analyze' tab for forms?",
			"answers": ["To view and categorize form submissions"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which type of field is suitable for alphanumeric input?",
			"answers": ["Single or multi line"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can forms be added to funnels and websites in the builder?",
			"answers": ["Using the native 'form element' in the page builder"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "When embedding forms in third-party platforms, what is the purpose of the 'Copy Embed' option?",
			"answers": ["To obtain the embed code for the form"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where would you connect a custom form to a calendar?",
			"answers": ["Calendar customization settings"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary focus of the tutorial?",
			"answers": ["Form-triggered workflow and notification"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of a trigger in a workflow?",
			"answers": ["To activate actions in the workflow"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How does the tutorial suggest redirecting 'users' (not leads) upon clicking the notification?",
			"answers": ["By using the 'Internal action' action in the workflow"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of setting up a workflow for survey submissions?",
			"answers": [
				"To automate notifications and actions based on survey responses"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of setting up a workflow for survey submissions?",
			"answers": [
				"To facilitate discussion, learning, networking, and knowledge sharing"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the client-facing portal discussed in the video?",
			"answers": ["To provide a link for customers to log-in or sign-up."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In a group, which roles can approve or decline membership requests? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Admins"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of reputation management in the system",
			"answers": [
				"To manage and improve online reviews improve SEO rankings and keep business content new and relevant"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users customize the review widget's appearance?",
			"answers": [
				"By selecting customizable options within the reputation management tab, located in the sub-account settings."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you customize the messaging for email and SMS review requests?",
			"answers": [
				"By enabling the respective options and editing the copy and messaging in the reputation settings section"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the prerequisite for accessing notification settings, as demonstrated in the video?",
			"answers": [
				"Being a user within that sub-account, or being 'logged in' as the user within the sub-account"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How does configuring user profile notifications contribute to workflow management?",
			"answers": [
				"It can reduce the number of internal notifications needed for day to day communications."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users access SMS compliance customization settings?",
			"answers": ["In the sub-account's settings"],
			"iframe": ""
		}
	]
}
